{
  "question": "At our usual bed-time, [MASK] and I were rolling away seaward with the Kentish letters. It was a night's journey in those coach times, but we had the mail to ourselves and did not find the night very tedious.",
  "answer": "Charley"
}
{
  "question": "She would not speak to [MASK] with half the certainty she felt on the subject, she would venture on little more than hints of what might be hereafter, of a possible attachment on his side, of the desirableness of the alliance, supposing such attachment to be real and returned.",
  "answer": "Anne"
}
{
  "question": "The country custom of unreserved comradeship out of doors during betrothal was the only custom she knew, and to her it had no strangeness; though it seemed oddly anticipative to [MASK] till he saw how normal a thing she, in common with all the other dairy-folk, regarded it.",
  "answer": "Clare"
}
{
  "question": "Now, the utterly unsurmised appearance of [MASK], tenanting my law-chambers of a Sunday morning, with his cadaverously gentlemanly _nonchalance_, yet withal firm and self-possessed, had such a strange effect upon me, that incontinently I slunk away from my own door, and did as desired.",
  "answer": "Bartleby"
}
{
  "question": "They lived a long time ago. That parrot one, I believe, is one of my great, great, great, great aunts. She looks rather like you, [MASK]--not as you look now but as you looked when you came here.",
  "answer": "Mary"
}
{
  "question": "Suddenly she came upon a little three-legged table, all made of solid glass; there was nothing on it except a tiny golden key, and [MASK]â€™s first thought was that it might belong to one of the doors of the hall; but, alas!",
  "answer": "Alice"
}
{
  "question": "[MASK] edged his horse around an impracticable slope of shale stuff and went on. The herder followed. When he was within twelve feet or so of the bottom, there was a sound of pebbles knocked loose in haste, a scrambling, and then came the impact of his body.",
  "answer": "Andy"
}
{
  "question": "But now [MASK] put his hand into his pocket, brought out a whistle, and blew upon it several modulated blasts that rang far across the heated air. I could not tell, of course, the meaning of the signal, but it instantly awoke my fears.",
  "answer": "Jim"
}
{
  "question": "Either to propitiate them, or to show his consideration for their feelings, he proceeded to offer them the apple which he held. The sight, unfortunately, was so comically apt in its illustration of the picture in her mind, the ruse was so transparent, that [MASK] was seized with laughter.",
  "answer": "Katharine"
}
{
  "question": "And tell my dear [MASK] not to give any directions about her clothes till she has seen me, for she does not know which are the best warehouses. Oh, brother, how kind you are! I know you will contrive it all.",
  "answer": "Lydia"
}
